Adedoja Adedamola

Web Developer and Graphic Designer



About Me

I am a 22year old web designer based in Pretoria, South Africa. I Specialize in Design, whether it is web (interactive, responsive) or branding (logo, business card, etc.) or posters and the development of web applications.

I transform clients ideas and projects into visually stimulating and well optimized websites that conform to the clients highest standards using latest technologies that also conform to industry standards.

I have more than 4 years' experience in Design and development and I am keen to learn more and extend my skills in programming as well as brand management.

Hobbies:

Reading, Music, Illustration & drawing, design, Music, Cinema, television, Internet Surfing.

Side Projects:

Mobile First Music Player (<u>www.Mwsiq.com</u>)

Ajaxified Music Player (<u>www.mwsiq.com/beta</u>)

Music News Blog(Blog.Mwsiq.com)

Magazine (<u>www.posh9jamag.com</u>)

MysolNG (www.mysolng.com)

Technical Skills

- * HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, JQuery Ajax
- * PHP/MYSQL
- Wordpress (Theme Development, Maintenance etc)
- MVC(Codelgniter)
- * Adobe Creative Suite6 (Illustrator, Dreamweaver, Fireworks, Photoshop)

In this Curriculum Vitae I have attempted to include only the most relevant information for readability and brevity. However, if you have any further questions about my experience or skills please feel free to email me at damdey@yahoo.com or see my personal website adeadedoja.github.com :

Employment History

New Horizons System Solutions, Ikeja, Lagos.

Web Development Instructor (October 2012-December 2013).

- Taught and trained students on the design and development of Website/Web applications using PHP.
- * Taught them from rudimentary HTML tags to Retrieving information previously stored in a database.

JWitlon Consulting, Egbeda, Lagos

Application Developer (August 2012- September 2012).

- * Developed a web app used by schools administrators to manager their school.
- The application was build using PHP,MYSQL, JQuery etc.

Freelance (October 2011 - Present)

- Designed and built custom websites for numerous clients, from start to finish, exclusively in WordPress
- Designed Web Applications powered by PHP/MYSQL for a lot of satisfied clients.

AGL Consulting LTD, Obanikoro, Lagos

Corp Member (December 2010 - September 2011).

* Installation and Maintenance of Office and Clients Computer Systems and softwares.

FORMAL EDUCATION & TRAINING

TSHWANE UNIVERSITY OF TECHNOLOGY

January 2014 - Present

BTech IT:Web and Application Development BOWEN UNIVERSITY

September 2007 - July 2010

2nd Class BSc. Computer Science

EDUCATIONAL ADVANCEMENT CENTRE

September 2005 - December 2006

Cambridge A'Levels Certificate